JENNY CITHERLET

P: 604 935 6304

E: jennycith@gmail.com

SUMMARY

I am a resourceful Email Specialist with experience in project management and CRM. I specialize in HTML/CSS transactional emails, content strategies, landing pages and marketing campaigns. I help improve click-through rate, list segmentation and to increase revenue.

I utilize strong organizational, planning and communication skills towards improving operational efficiency. I worked with Agile/Scrum methodologies, and I have a passion for people and technology. With a comprehensive background in digital media and web technologies, I am a problem-solver with excellent analytical and negotiation skills. I am committed to providing the best customer experience as well as continuous improvement.

SKILLS

- 8+ yrs. of experience in HTML emails, landing pages and marketing Automation
- Experience in list segmentation
- Strong working knowledge of CMS, HTML, CSS, email client specificities, A/B testing
- Experience using ERPs (Oracle, SAP for HR), Salesforce Marketing Cloud
- Dynamic and reliable team-player with proven organizational and communication skills
- Customer service attitude and trustworthy, positive approach. Experience working remotely
- Create, test and maintain web pages with WP and other CMS

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

EMAIL DEVELOPER — IMPLEMENTATION SPECIALIST

APRIL 2023 TO PRESENT

(FREELANCE)

- Building collateral (HTML transactional email, Marketing campaigns and landing pages) for clients.
- Advocate best practices in email design, content strategy, and digital marketing using CSS to meet design specifications of customers for the specific application.
- Use enterprise-level email service platform to manage email lists, conduct audience segmentation and A/B testing, and deployment.
- Manage projects involving clients and various internal departments.
- Create, test, and maintain web pages with WP and other CMS.

GUESTFOLIO - CENDYN, WHISTLER, BC

May 2014 - March 2023

ACCOUNT PRODUCER & CONTENT SPECIALIST (CONTRACTOR & EMPLOYEE)

Guestfolio, an award-winning and trusted guest engagement platform for hospitality data. We work in partnership with hoteliers and provide an integrated single-source solution that manages all day-to-day transactional communications, guest satisfaction and digital marketing programs.

- Responsible for on-boarding and building new accounts. Uses creative and digital skills to build collateral (HTML/CSS automated email marketing solution, newsletter, Mobile Concierge app & survey) for our hotel clients worldwide.
- Improved email content and design to improve open & click rate by +34%. Improved list segmentation and increased property revenue.

MIKE WIEGELE HELICOPTER SKIING, BLUE RIVER, BC LEAD SKI GUIDE

NOVEMBER 2006 - MARCH 2018 (PART-TIME & FULL-TIME)

- Provide international guests with one of the best ski experiences on the planet while managing risk in an uncontrolled mountain environment.
- Mentor assistant guides with risk management and customer service.

WHISTLER HELI-SKIING, WHISTLER, B.C., CANADA GROUND OFFICE MANAGER & ADMINISTRATOR

DECEMBER 2004 - FEBRUARY 2014

- Managed and trained team of 15 Sales Associates
- Monitored and tracked accounts payable/receivable
- Acted as the main contact for booking agents and provided booking agents with Product Knowledge Sessions
- Built and maintained strong business partnerships to deliver a high level of service
- Created and implemented tools & processes for tracking reservations and seat bookings
- Coordinated administration & communication on a daily basis

ADDITIONAL SKILLS

- Experience working with Agile methodologies
- Proficient in Adobe Creative Suite, Microsoft Office, Google Docs, Asana, Slack, Teams, Figma
- Experience using ERPs (Oracle, SAP)
- Instructional Skill Workshop
- Fluent in French/English

EDUCATION

0	Web Development Bootcamp	Lighthouse Labs, Vancouver, BC	2020
0	Digital Marketing & Social Media	British Columbia Institute of Technology	2019
0	Web Technologies	British Columbia Institute of Technology	2013
0	Business Diploma	Ecole Supérieure de Commerce, Switzerland	2002